A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Grants, RG 5 FA1403
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Dance, 1964-2006; 10; 23.17 Cubic Feet 61 letter document boxes
  - Cambodia, 11.2
    - University of California, Los Angeles, APEX, 702-00-20078-203.1, 2000 (Box 537, Folder 7)
    - Eiko and Koma, 100-00-23124-203.3, 2003 (Box 537, Folder 8)
    - Hun, Pen, 100-00-24133-203.3, 2004 (Box 537, Folder 9)
    - Hun, Pen, 634-00-23085-203.1, 634-00-22111-203.1, 2002-2003 (Box 538, Folder 1)
    - New England Foundation for the Arts, 100-00-20059-203.1, 2000 (Box 538, Folder 2)
    - New England Foundation for the Arts, 100-00-20026-203.3, 2000 (Box 538, Folder 3)
    - New England Foundation for the Arts, Proeng Chhieng?s Travel, 100-00-22145-203.3, 2002 (Box 538, Folder 4)
    - New England Foundation for the Arts, Dance, Spirit of Cambodia, 100-00-21068-203.1, 2001 (Box 539, Folder 1)
    - Proeung, Chhieng, JDR 3rd Award, 705-00-99145-203.1, 1999 (Box 539, Folder 2)
    - Proeung, Chhieng, 100-00-22143-203.3, 2002 (Box 539, Folder 3)
  - China, 10.3
    - Lu, Chih-Ming, B-7505, B-7606, 1975-1976 (Box 539, Folder 4)
    - Chiang Ching Dance Company, Inc., DF-7951, 1979 (Box 540, Folder 1)
    - National Dance Institute, DF-8560, B-8530, 1985 (Box 636, Folder 1)
    - American Dance Festival (ADF), B-8567, 1985 (Box 540, Folder 2)
    - Chiang Ching, EC-8205, 1982 (Box 540, Folder 3)
    - Zhang, Ying, B-8732, DF-8894, 1987-1988 (Box 540, Folder 4)
    - Elisa Monte Dance Company, DF-8727, 1987 (Box 540, Folder 5)
    - National Dance Institute, EC-8607, DF-90109, 1986; 1990 (Box 541, Folder 1-2)
    - Nikolais-Louis Foundation, DF-8979, 1989 (Box 541, Folder 3)
    - Yao, Shu-Fen, B-9029, 1990 (Box 541, Folder 4)
    - International Dance Alliance, DF-9395, 1993 (Box 541, Folder 5)
    - New York University, 100-00-95016-203.000-3, 1995 (Box 541, Folder 6)
    - Lin, Hwai-Min, EC-7868, DF-7890, 1978 (Box 541, Folder 7)
    - Connecticut College, 100-00-98107-203.3, 1998 (Box 541, Folder 8)
    - American Dance Festival, 100-00-97041-203.1, 1997 (Box 541, Folder 9)
    - American Dance Festival, DF-8812, EC-9106, 1988; 1991 (Box 541, Folder 10)
    - American Dance Festival, 100-00-95019-203.000-3, 1995 (Box 541, Folder 11)
    - American Dance Festival, 100-00-21020-203.2, 2001 (Box 633, Folder 1)
    - American Dance Festival, 100-00-99013-203.2, 1999 (Box 633, Folder 2)
    - American Dance Festival, 100-00-97041-203.1, 1997 (Box 633, Folder 3)
    - Foundation for Independent Artists, Inc., 100-00-95121-203.000-3, 1995 (Box 542, Folder 1)
    - Ho, Hsiao-Mei, B-9028, 1990 (Box 542, Folder 2)
    - Lin, Hwai-Min, EC-7868, DF-7890, 1978 (Box 542, Folder 3)
    - Wong, Yen Lu, EC-8686, 1986 (Box 542, Folder 4)
    - Chiang, Ching-Beijing Dance Academy, 479-00-96038-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 542, Folder 5)
    - Cross Performance, Inc., 100-00-99108-203.000-3, 1999 (Box 542, Folder 6)
    - Dance Theater Workshop, 100-00-22135-203.1, 2002 (Box 542, Folder 7)
    - Guangdong ATV Academy of Performing Arts, 706-00-22090-203.1, 2002 (Box 542, Folder 8)
    - Guangdong ATV Academy of Performing Arts, 100-00-21067-203.1, 2001 (Box 633, Folder 4)
    - Nai-Ni Chen Dance Company, 100-00-20148-203.3, 2000 (Box 542, Folder 9)
    - Ou, Jian-ping, DF-93103, 1993 (Box 543, Folder 1)
    - Ou, Jian-ping, EC-8803, DF-8895, 1988 (Box 543, Folder 2)
    - Reynolds, Phil, 100-00-22153-203.3, 2002 (Box 543, Folder 3)
    - Wei, Danny Ye, 100-00-21057-203.1, 100-00-20040-203.1, 2000 (Box 543, Folder 4)
    - Xing, Liang, 452-00-95058-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 544, Folder 1)
    - Shi, Xuan and Zhou, Niannian, 100-00-21015-203.2, 2001 (Box 544, Folder 2)
    - Chen, Weiya, 5451-00-94047-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 544, Folder 3)
    - Hou, Yin, 100-00-21055-203.1, 2001 (Box 544, Folder 4)
    - Pearlman, Ellen, 707-00-24051-203.1, 2004 (Box 545, Folder 1)
    - Huang, Dou Dou, 100-00-25132-203.3, 100-00-23008-203.2, 2003 (Box 545, Folder 2)
    - Sang, Ji Jia, 100-00-99028-203.3, 100-00-98041-203.1, 1998 (Box 545, Folder 3)
    - Sang, Ji Jia, 100-00-24122-203.3, 2004 (Box 545, Folder 4)
    - Jin, Xing, EC-8823, 1988 (Box 546, Folder 1)
    - Shen, Wei, 100-00-95122-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 546, Folder 2)
    - Wen, Hui, 100-00-98007-203.2, 100-00-96032-203.2, 1994-1998 (Box 546, Folder 3-4)
    - Xu, Rui, 100-00-25004-203.3, 100-00-24041-203.1, 2004 (Box 547, Folder 1)
    - Connecticut College, 100-00-25041-203.1, 2005 (Box 547, Folder 2)
    - Yang Meigi, 705-00-22146-203.1 (Box 572, Folder 5)
  - Hong Kong, 10.4
    - Chan, Clement Kan Ming, B-8743(67)R, 1987 (Box 547, Folder 3)
    - Law, Kimberly Wing Fan, B-8744(67)R, 1987 (Box 547, Folder 4)
    - Tso, Po-lin, EC-8820(162-168)R, 1988 (Box 547, Folder 5)
    - Woo, Po Yee, EC-8821(162-168)R, 1988 (Box 547, Folder 6)
    - Chung, Jocelyn Bik Ha, DD-9018(304), 1990 (Box 547, Folder 7)
    - Dance-Hong Kong (HKAP), Fifth H. K. International Dance Conference, B-89111(HK), 1989 (Box 547, Folder 8)
    - Hang, Angela Cam Tho, DD-9017(304), 1990 (Box 548, Folder 1)
    - International Sinodance Association, B-8954(HK), 1989 (Box 548, Folder 2)
    - Ma, Chi Pang, B-8942(252), 1989 (Box 548, Folder 3)
    - University of Hawaii, B-8955(HK), 1989 (Box 548, Folder 4)
    - Wong, Ting Lam, B-8943(HK), 1989 (Box 548, Folder 5)
    - Chau, Selina Kah Yan, 497-00-96025-203.00-4, 1996 (Box 548, Folder 6)
    - Chow, Sally Hung, 497-00-96026-203.000-4, 1996 (Box 548, Folder 7)
    - Cheung, Sau Mui (Vanessa), DD-9224(386), 1992 (Box 548, Folder 8)
    - Chu, Sin Yi, 470-00-94022-203.000-4, 1994 (Box 548, Folder 9)
    - City Contemporary Dance, 507-00-97120-203.000-2, 1997 (Box 548, Folder 10)
    - City Contemporary Dance Company, 507-00-98064-203.1, 1998 (Box 548, Folder 11)
    - Ford, Niles, 100-00-98004-203.3, 1998 (Box 548, Folder 12)
    - Fong, Force Chun Kuen, 482-00-95017-203.000-4, 1995 (Box 549, Folder 1)
    - Ho, Chui Leung, 528-00-97031-4, 1997 (Box 549, Folder 2)
    - Ho, Snady Wing Kiu, 565-00-98039-203.4, 1998 (Box 549, Folder 3)
    - Hung, Marie Mei-ying, 507-00-97067-203.1, 1997 (Box 549, Folder 4)
    - H. T. Dance Company, 100-00-96111-203.000-3, 1996 (Box 549, Folder 5)
    - Kwok, Ken Wai Kit, 565-00-98037-203.4, 1998 (Box 549, Folder 6)
    - Lam, Allen Wai Yuen, B-9355(HK), 1993 (Box 549, Folder 7)
    - Lam, Wai Yuen, B-8941(252), 1989 (Box 549, Folder 8)
    - Law, Wing Tsz, EC-8819(162-168)R, 1988 (Box 549, Folder 9)
    - Lee, Nim Chun (Charissa), DD-9118(326), 1991 (Box 549, Folder 10)
    - Pun, Siu-fai, B-8953(HK), B-89110(HK), 1989 (Box 550, Folder 1)
    - Seth, Philip, EC-8881-(HK)R, 1988 (Box 550, Folder 2)
    - So, Mei Po, 470-00-94023-203.000-4, 1994 (Box 550, Folder 3)
    - Tam, Yuk Fong (Vivian), DD-9225(386), 1992 (Box 550, Folder 4)
    - Tsui, Wing Man, DD-9318(403), 1993 (Box 550, Folder 5)
    - Tan, Selina, DF-9229, 1992 (Box 550, Folder 6)
    - Yip, Choi Fung, DD-9319(403), 1993 (Box 550, Folder 7)
    - Yu, Jacky Yan Wah, B-9074(306), 1990 (Box 550, Folder 8)
    - Yuen, Chi Fai, DD-9119(326), 1991 (Box 550, Folder 9)
    - Yu, Congo Yin Fan, 497-00-96027-203.000-4, 1996 (Box 550, Folder 10)
    - Zuni Icosahedron Company, B-8956, 1989 (Box 551, Folder 1)
    - Cheung, Pui, 590-00-99112.4, 1999 (Box 551, Folder 2)
    - Dance HK-NY, 507-00-98065-203.1, 591-00-99122-203.4, 1998; 1999 (Box 551, Folder 3)
    - Fai, Pun Siu, 100-00-99129-203.3, 1999 (Box 551, Folder 4)
    - Hong Kong Dance Alliance, 100-00-22140-203.3, 2002 (Box 551, Folder 5)
    - Kwan, Ho Ki, 610-00-210125-203.4, 2001 (Box 551, Folder 6)
    - Kwok, Huiwah, B-8856(HK), DF-9299, EC-88104(HK)R, 1988; 1992 (Box 552, Folder 1)
    - Lam, Po, 610-00-20126-203.4, 2000 (Box 552, Folder 2)
    - Chan, Abby Man Yee, 452-00-96058-203.000-1, 332-95060-1, 1995; 1996 (Box 552, Folder 3)
    - Leung, Mei Kar, 528-00-97030-4, 1997 (Box 552, Folder 4)
    - Ma, Victor and Yim, Mandy, 502-00-96062-203.1, 507-00-97144-203.1, 1996; 1997 (Box 552, Folder 5)
    - Mui, Cynthia Cheuk Yin, 507-00-97010-203.2, 1997 (Box 552, Folder 6)
    - Wong, Andy, 340-00-94058-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 553, Folder 1)
    - Wong, Chin Bong, 565-00-98038-203.4, 1998 (Box 553, Folder 2)
    - Wong, Dominic Dick Man, 482-00-95018-203.000-4, 1995 (Box 553, Folder 3)
    - Yau, Catherine, 589-00-99089-203.1, 1999 (Box 553, Folder 4)
    - Wong, Wendy, 567-00-98063-203.1, 1998 (Box 553, Folder 5)
    - Luo, Fan. 658-00-23056-203.1, 2003 (Box 553, Folder 6)
    - Yin, Mei (formerly known as Yan, Mui), EC-8551, DF-85101, 1985 (Box 553, Folder 7)
  - India, 10.5
    - Kalakshetra Academy of Arts, B-7059, B-7258-AIP, 1970; 1972 (Box 554, Folder 1)
    - Nassif, Anna, B-6660, 1966 (Box 554, Folder 2)
    - Ram, Bali, B-6427, B-6609, 1964; 1966 (Box 554, Folder 3)
    - ASEA, Kerala Kalamandalam Kathakali Company, DF-7177, 1971 (Box 554, Folder 4)
    - Darom, Ari, DF-8125, 1981 (Box 554, Folder 5)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, EC-8504, 1985 (Box 554, Folder 6)
    - Asia Society, Maharaj, Birju, DF-8557, 1985 (Box 554, Folder 7)
    - Sahoo, Kadar Nath (Dance Notation Bureau),B-8009, DF-8050, 1980 (Box 554, Folder 8)
    - Seraikella Chhau as Taught by Kedar Nath Sahoo, 1980 (Box 554, Folder 9)
    - Battery Dance Company, 100-00-95113-203.000-3, 1995 (Box 555, Folder 1)
    - Coorlawala, Asha, B-7132, 1971 (Box 555, Folder 2)
    - Lotus Fine Arts, DF-9115, Canceled, 1991 (Box 555, Folder 3)
    - Shah, Purnima, B-9122, 1991 (Box 555, Folder 4)
    - Balasaraswati School of Indian Music and Dance, 100-00-97026-203.000-3, 1997 (Box 555, Folder 5)
    - Dubey, Gopal, B-8624, 1986 (Box 555, Folder 6)
    - Harma, Bharat, B-8119, DF-8234, 1981-1982 (Box 556, Folder 1)
    - Cornell University, 702-00-23052-203.1, 2003 (Box 556, Folder 2)
    - Dandacate, Rohini, 706-00-25072-203.1, 2005 (Box 556, Folder 3)
    - Gere, David, 706-00-23068-203.1, 2003 (Box 556, Folder 4)
    - Knight, Douglas, 706-00-22087-203.1, 2002 (Box 556, Folder 5)
    - Kothari, Sunil, B-9234, 1992 (Box 557, Folder 1)
    - Meduri, Avanthi, B-8783, B-8747(26), B-8853(36), B-8947(26), B-9035(26), B-9130, EC-9308(26), 1987-1993 (Box 557, Folder 2)
    - Sen, Surupa, 100-00-20029-203.1, 2000 (Box 557, Folder 3)
    - Kalakshetra Academy of Arts, B-7059, 1970 (Box 941, Folder 3)
  - Indonesia, 10.6
    - Akademi Seni Tari Indonesia: Books, B-7538-AIP, 1975 (Box 557, Folder 4)
    - Dance-Indoneisa, Bhakti Vidya Buddhaya Foundation (BVB), (Videocorder), Jajasan Bhakti Vidya Buddhaya, Krida Beksa Wirama Dance Conservatory of BVB Foundation Bhakti Vudya Buddhaya Foundation (BVB), Dance-Indo, B-7174-MCR, B-7366-MCR (Box 558, Folder 1)
    - Soedarsono, (ASTI), B-7060, B-70103, DF-71104, B-7258-AIP, B-7640-AIP, DF-7773, DF-7894, 1970-1978 (Box 558, Folder 2)
    - ASTI (Box 558, Folder 3)
    - Supartha, I Gusti Agung Ngurah, 1985 (Box 943, Folder 3)
    - Supartha, I Gusti Ngurah, DF-8201, 1982 (Box 558, Folder 4)
    - University of California, Los Angeles, B-8419, 1984 (Box 558, Folder 5)
    - Wiratini, Ni Made, Master?s Thesis, Condong and Its Roles in Balinese Dance-Drama, DD-89995(263), 1991 (Box 558, Folder 6)
    - Jakarta Institute of the Arts Dance Company, DF-8446, 1984 (Box 636, Folder 2)
    - LPKJ, Director, Jakarta Institute of the Arts, Photo Album, 1976 January 26 (Box 949, Folder 7)
    - Elisa Monte Dance Company, EC-8893, 1988 (Box 558, Folder 7)
    - New York Public Library-Dance Collection, DD-8921(247), 1989 (Box 559, Folder 1)
    - Sipala, Wiwiek, R-8224(15), 1982 (Box 559, Folder 2)
    - Soedarsono, Winotokusumo, DF-8110, B-8039, B-8114(4), 1980-1981 (Box 559, Folder 3)
    - Wiratini, Ni Made, B-88113(26)R, DF-8781, DD-8897(175), DD-88110(176), DF-8981, DD-8985(263), 1988 (Box 559, Folder 4)
    - Hoemar, Linda, EC-8673, B-8733, DF-8879, 1986-1988 (Box 560, Folder 1)
    - Body Tjak Project, B-9020, 1990 (Box 560, Folder 2)
    - Jacob's Pillow Project Festival, Sardono, B-9325, 1993 (Box 560, Folder 3)
    - Murgiyanto, Sal, DD-9094(313), B-9037(26), B-89108(26), DD-8980(245), EC-8905(26), 1989-1990 (Box 560, Folder 4)
    - Murgiyanto, Sal, Not Grant Payment - Correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 561, Folder 1)
    - Murgiyanto, Sal, Payment of Grants (Box 561, Folder 2)
    - Siegel, Marcia, DF-8985, 1989 (Box 561, Folder 3)
    - Dibia, I Wayan, B-8056, DF-8063, 1980 (Box 562, Folder 1)
    - Ibnur, Tom, 477-00-94113-203.000-4, 1994 (Box 562, Folder 2)
    - Jakarta Institute of the Arts, DF-93107, 1993 (Box 562, Folder 3)
    - Abidin, Linda Hoemar, 100-00-99033-203.3, 1999 (Box 562, Folder 4)
    - Bates College, Bates Dance Festival, 100-00-99107-203.00-3, 1999 (Box 562, Folder 5)
    - Bellows, Laura Jane, 706-00-97080-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 562, Folder 6)
    - Brenner, Janis, 100-00-21044-203.3, 2001 (Box 562, Folder 7)
    - Crosspulse, Inc., 100-00-99044-203.000-1, 1999 (Box 562, Folder 8)
    - Dibia, I Wayan, R-8221(18), 1982 (Box 563, Folder 1)
    - Dibia, I Wayan, Wiratini, Ni Made, 498-00-980028-203.4, 1998 (Box 563, Folder 2)
    - Hartati, 100-00-99133-203.1, 1999 (Box 563, Folder 3)
    - Indonesian Dance Festival, 100-00-22059-203.1, 2002 (Box 563, Folder 4)
    - Indonesian Dance Festival, 706-00-96072-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 563, Folder 5)
    - Indonesian Dance Festival, 100-00-99046-203.000-1, 1999 (Box 564, Folder 1)
    - Kusumo, Sardono, 100-00-20150-203.3, 2000 (Box 564, Folder 2)
    - Kusumo, Sardono, DF-8679, DF-9415, DF-8827, 1986-1994 (Box 564, Folder 3)
    - Larasati, Diyah, 525-00-99119-203.4, 525-00-98111-203.4, 702-0099057-203.1, 702-00-98054-203.1, Folder 1 (Box 564, Folder 4)
    - Larasati, Diyah, 100-00-20134-203.3, 525-0099057-203.1, 525-00-99119-203.4, 525-00-98111-203.4, 702-00-98054-203.1, 525-00-97118-203.4, 702-00-97059-203.1, 1997-1999 (Box 564, Folder 5)
    - Larasati, Diyah, 100-00-20134-203.3, 525-0099057-203.1, 525-00-99119-203.4, 525-00-98111-203.4, 702-00-98054-203.1, 525-00-97118-203.4, 702-00-97059-203.1, 1997-1999 (Box 565, Folder 1)
    - Loedin, Iskander Kama, 100-00-97036-203.00-1, 534-00-97126-203.000-4, 1997 (Box 565, Folder 2)
    - Murgiyanto, Sal, 100-00-94092-203.000-3, 1994 (Box 565, Folder 3)
    - Murgiyanto, Sal, 100-00-20024-203.3, 100-00-99032-203.3, 1999-2000 (Box 565, Folder 4)
    - Sakti, Boi, 100-00-99134-203.1, 1999 (Box 565, Folder 5)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts, 100-21024-203.2, 2001 (Box 566, Folder 1)
    - Sriman, Sukarji, 100-00-21048-203.3, 704-00-2007-203.1, 100-00-20165-203.3, 100-00-99039-203.1, Folder 1, 2000-2001 (Box 566, Folder 2)
    - Sriman, Sukarji, 100-00-97038-203.000-1, 534-00-97125-203.000-4, 1997 (Box 566, Folder 3)
    - Supriyanto, Eko, 702-00-21025-203.2, 525-00-99118-203.4, 525-00-98115-203.4, 525-00-20164-203.4, 702-00-99061-203.1, 525-00-98057-203.1, 1998-2001 (Box 566, Folder 4)
    - Utama, Indra, 702-00-97061-203.000-1, 525-00-97117-203.4, 1997 (Box 566, Folder 5)
    - Dance Advance, 100-00-24121-203.3, 2004 (Box 567, Folder 1)
    - Cerita, I Nyoman, 702-00-24003-203.2, 702-00-22075-203.1 (Box 567, Folder 2)
    - Kusumaningrum, Restu, 100-00-20045-203.1, 2000 (Box 567, Folder 3)
    - Mei, Yin, 100-00-21136-203.3, 2001 (Box 567, Folder 4)
    - Miroto, Martinus, 702-00-94035-203.000-1, B-9345(26), EC-9303, DD-9298(393), 1992-1994 (Box 568, Folder 1-2)
    - Miroto, Martinus, 100-00-24120-203.3, 2004 (Box 568, Folder 3)
  - Japan, 10.7
    - Hijakata, Tatsumi, B-6936 Canceled, 1969 (Box 568, Folder 4)
    - Sagisaka, Yuriko, B-6718, DF-6789, 1967 (Box 569, Folder 1)
    - Endo, Yoshihisa, B-7038, DF-7185, EC-7131, 1971 (Box 569, Folder 2)
    - Theater of the Open Eye, DF-7959, 1979 (Box 569, Folder 3)
    - Laura Dean Dancers, B-8426(30)R, 1984 (Box 569, Folder 4)
    - Wood, Margaret (City Center), B-8584(30)R, 1985 (Box 569, Folder 5)
    - The Asia Society, DF-8813, 1988 (Box 569, Folder 6)
    - Austro Arts, DF-8669, 1986 (Box 569, Folder 7)
    - Dance Gallery (Lewitsky, Bella), B-8770(30)R, 1987 (Box 569, Folder 8)
    - Lewitzky (Bella) Dance Co., US Organization (Box 569, Folder 9)
    - Ruby Shang and Company, Dancers, B-87107(30)R, 1987 (Box 570, Folder 1)
    - Shang, Ruby, B-8430(30)R, 1984 (Box 570, Folder 2)
    - Hasegawa, Roku, B-9061(30), 1990 (Box 570, Folder 3)
    - Kasami, Yasuko, B-8867(30)R, 1988 (Box 570, Folder 4)
    - Cummings, Blondell, B-8873(30)R, 1988 (Box 570, Folder 5)
    - Childs, Lucinda, EC-8409(30)R, 1984 (Box 570, Folder 6)
    - Nakajima, Natsue, B-8798(30)R, 1987 (Box 571, Folder 1)
    - Fleming, Maureen, B-9068(30), 1990 (Box 571, Folder 2)
    - Goh Productions, 704-00-97099-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 571, Folder 3)
    - Hahn, Tomi, B-9268(56), 1992 (Box 571, Folder 4)
    - Jacob's Pillow Dance Festival, 7004-00-96089-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 571, Folder 5)
    - Ichikawa, Miyabi, B-86102(30)R, 1986 (Box 571, Folder 6)
    - Jacob's Pillow Dance Festival, 704-00-95086-203.00-1, 1995 (Box 571, Folder 7)
    - Knowles, Alison, 100-00-95109-203.000-3, 1995 (Box 572, Folder 1)
    - P.S. 122, 704-00-97084-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 572, Folder 2)
    - Yonei, Sumie, B-8540(30)R, 1985 (Box 572, Folder 3)
    - Tanaka, Min, DF-8303, 1983 (Box 572, Folder 4)
    - Body Weather Laboratory, Min Tanaka, 100-00-20128-203.3, 2000 (Box 572, Folder 6)
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music, 100-00-99130-203.3, 1999 (Box 572, Folder 7)
    - Cornfield, Ellen, 100-00-20124-203.3, 2000 (Box 572, Folder 8)
    - d-NET, 100-00-20025-203.3, 2000 (Box 572, Folder 9)
    - Fenley, Molissa, B-90105(30), 1990 (Box 572, Folder 10)
    - Ito, Kyoto, 1997 (Box 572, Folder 11)
    - Hunter College Dance, DF-8597, 1985 (Box 636, Folder 3)
    - Hong, Sin Cha, B-8698(30)R, 1986 (Box 573, Folder 1)
    - International Summer School of Dance, 100-00-22142-203.3, 2002 (Box 573, Folder 2)
    - International Summer School of Dance, 704-00-99090-203.000-1, 1999 (Box 573, Folder 3)
    - Japan Society, US-Japan Exchange Residencies, 704-00-21117-203.1, 2001 (Box 573, Folder 4)
    - National Performance Network, 100-00-99149-203.3, 1999 (Box 573, Folder 5)
    - Portland State University, 704-00-99093-203.000-1, 1999 (Box 573, Folder 6)
    - Sakamoto, Kosei, 605-00-21108-203.1, 2001 (Box 573, Folder 7)
    - Sato, Norikazu, 534-00-97124-203.000-4, 1997 (Box 574, Folder 1)
    - Sato, Norikazu, 488-00-96076-203.000-1, 100-00-96108-203.000-3, 1996 (Box 574, Folder 2)
    - ST Spot Yokohama, 100-00-22003-203.3, 2002 (Box 574, Folder 3)
    - University of California, Los Angeles, APEX, 704-00-20110-203.1, 2000 (Box 574, Folder 4)
    - Yamada, Setsuko, B-9380(30), 1993 (Box 574, Folder 5)
    - Yamazaki, Kota, 534-00-97127-203.000-4, 1997 (Box 574, Folder 6)
    - Yerba Buena Center for the Arts, 704-00-98093-203.1, 1998 (Box 575, Folder 1)
    - Amano, Yukiko, 686-00-24075-203.1, 2004 (Box 575, Folder 2)
    - Danspace, 704-00-25140-203.3, 2005 (Box 575, Folder 3)
    - Cardone, Alissa, 704-00-24082-203.1, 2004 (Box 575, Folder 4)
    - Fenley, Molissa, 517-00-98047-203.1, 1998 (Box 575, Folder 5)
    - American Dance Festival, Akiko Kitamura, 704-00-23019-203.2, 2003 (Box 575, Folder 6)
    - Galilee, clove, 704-00-25087-203.1, 2005 (Box 575, Folder 7)
    - Heteruma, Nagako, 704-00-22095-203.1, 2002 (Box 575, Folder 8)
    - International Summer School of Dance, 704-00-24089-203.1, 2004 (Box 576, Folder 1)
    - International Summer School of Dance, 704-00-23020-203.2, 2003 (Box 576, Folder 2)
    - Iwabuchi, Takiko, 586-00-20095-203.1, 2000 (Box 576, Folder 3)
    - Japan Society, Exchange Residencies, 704-00-24090-203.1, 2004 (Box 576, Folder 4)
    - New England Foundation for the Arts, 704-00-23084-203.1, 2003 (Box 576, Folder 5)
    - June Watanabe in Company, 704-00-24013-203.2, 2004 (Box 576, Folder 6)
    - Murobushi, Ko, 648-00-23075-203.1, 2003 (Box 576, Folder 7)
    - New Jersey Center for the Performing Arts, 704-00-24091-203.1, 2004 (Box 577, Folder 1)
    - Tanaka, Min, 686-00-24081-203.1, 2004 (Box 577, Folder 2)
    - Pearson, S. and P. Widrig, 704-00-23081-203.1, 2003 (Box 577, Folder 3)
    - Yanaihara, Mikuni, 628-00-22098-203.1, 2002 (Box 577, Folder 4)
  - Korea, 10.8
    - Lim, Sung-Nam, IIE, B-6938, DF-6897, DF-6899, DF-68100, 1965; 1968 (Box 577, Folder 5)
    - Kang, Song-Won, EC-9013, 1990 (Box 577, Folder 6)
    - The St. Ann Center, DF-8993, 1989 (Box 578, Folder 1)
    - Park, Il Kyu, Df-8473, B-8424, 1984 (Box 578, Folder 2)
    - Lee, Sun Ock-Samulnori Institute, 494-00-96074-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 578, Folder 3-4)
    - Ahn, Ae Soon, 498-00-96103-203.00-4, 469-00-95089-203.000-1, 1995; 1996 (Box 578, Folder 5)
    - Trinity College, 100-00-98033-203.000-4, 1998 (Box 578, Folder 6)
    - Zen Temple of Cresskill, 100-00-95020-203.000-.3, 1995 (Box 578, Folder 7)
    - Juksan International Arts Festival, 100-00-20038-203.3, 2000 (Box 578, Folder 8)
    - Kang, Manhong, B-8841, 1988 (Box 579, Folder 1)
    - Sohn, In-Young, B-9322, 702-00-94040-203.000-1, 100-00-95023-203.000-1, 1993-1995 (Box 579, Folder 2)
    - University of Hawaii, 702-00-22079-203.1 (Box 579, Folder 3)
  - Malaysia, 10.9
    - Dance Theater Workshop, 479-00-951118-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 580, Folder 1)
    - Dance Theater Workshop, 100-00-95033-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 580, Folder 2)
    - Ahmad, Azanin, DF-8336, 1983 (Box 580, Folder 3)
    - D'Cruz, Marion, DF-8109, 1981 (Box 580, Folder 5)
    - Ibrahim, Ramil, 100-00-98121-203.3, 702-00-96053.1, 1996; 1998 (Box 580, Folder 6)
    - Loke, Soh Kim, 100-00-97039-203.1, 100-00-98117-203.3, 1997; 1998 (Box 581, Folder 1-2)
    - Nor, Mohd Anis Md., 706-00-98076-203.1, 1998 (Box 581, Folder 3)
    - Northwest Asian American Theatre, 100-00-20013-203.2, 2000 (Box 581, Folder 4)
    - University of Malaysia, 100-00-20141-203.3, 2001 (Box 581, Folder 5)
  - Philippines, 10.10
    - Guzman, Alex de, B-9235, 1992 (Box 580, Folder 4)
    - Center of Philippines, Cultural Center of Philippines Dance Workshop, Koner, P., B-7360, 1973 (Box 581, Folder 6)
    - Cultural Center of Philippines Dance Workshop, American Dance Teacher-Choreographer, Koner, Pauline, American Choreographer, B-7360, 1973 (Box 581, Folder 7)
    - Reyes, Alice, Sarah Lawrence College, B-6945, 1969 (Box 581, Folder 8)
    - Villaurz, B. Esteban, B-74102, 1974 (Box 582, Folder 1)
    - Cultural Center of Philippines Dance Workshop (CCP), American Teacher:Shepard, Evelyn R., DF-7397, 1973 (Box 582, Folder 2)
    - Barredo, Josephine, American Ballet Center, B-7720, 1977 (Box 582, Folder 3)
    - Layag, Luis P., DF-7559, 1975 (Box 582, Folder 4)
    - Molina, Manuel B., III, B-7432, DF-7381, 1973; 1974 (Box 582, Folder 5)
    - Dance Perspectives Foundation, R. G. Alejandro, Monograph "Sayaw-Silangan", DF-7342, 1973 (Box 582, Folder 6)
    - Ballet Philippines, DD-8596(440)R, 1985 (Box 582, Folder 7)
    - Jardin, Nestor, EC-8334, DF-8910(FEDAPT), 1983; 1989 (Box 582, Folder 8)
    - Sabas, Hazel, B-8937, B-9025, 1989; 1990 (Box 583, Folder 1)
    - Alcedo, R. Patrick, 702-00-21085-203.1, 702-00-20076-203.1, 2000; 2001 (Box 583, Folder 2)
    - Alcedo, R. Patrick, 702-00-99062-203.1, 702-00-98058-203.1, 702-00-97062-203.1, 702-00-96100-203.1, 1998; 1999 (Box 583, Folder 3)
    - Ballet Philippines, 100-00-21010-203.3, 2001 (Box 584, Folder 1)
    - Jacinto, Joel, 706-00-98077-203.1, 1998 (Box 584, Folder 2)
    - Jackson, Kristin, DF-9293, 1992 (Box 584, Folder 3)
    - Pearl Ubungan and Dancers, 100-00-20015-203.2, 2000 (Box 584, Folder 4)
    - Villaruz, Basilio Esteban, 100-00-20002-203.3, DF-9101, 1991 (Box 584, Folder 5)
    - Ballet Philippines, 655-00-23099-203.1, 2003 (Box 584, Folder 6)
    - UCLA-APPEX, 655-00-24022-203.2, 2004 (Box 584, Folder 7)
    - Villaruz, B. Estaban, 100-00-22159-203.3, 2002 (Box 584, Folder 8)
  - Singapore, 10.11
    Singapore
    - Pick of the Crop Dance Company, 100-00-98131-203.4, 1998 (Box 584, Folder 9)
  - Sri Lanka, 10.12
    - Reed, Susan, EC-9109(77), 1991 (Box 584, Folder 10)